[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10 || 99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "From the Ashes of Caer Dun",
        "Description": "After the sacking of Caer Dun, the Soulwardens risk losing everything if the Tempest strikes again. In order to survive, they must relocate to the presumed safety of Ebonscale Reach.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"No. We must regroup.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Regroup! Where!? I thought we were safe here, but I was wrong... about so much.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Proud Caer Dun… now in shambles.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thank you for finding the other Soulwardens. I should have exercised more caution. But I never imagined the Corrupted… here?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Discord and Balance",
        "Description": "With the reveal that the Tempest can see through your eyes, the Soulwardens remain on the verge of destruction. On counsel from Sun Fuchun, a plan is devised to seek out her old master who might be able to help if he has not fallen to Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"No one is secure with me.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You mean… of course. The thought had crossed my mind that the Tempest was seeing through your eyes.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If Master Qi has fallen to Corruption… this day will grow darker indeed.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hold on! What are you thinking, coming this way? I finally find a spot of safety, and you come waltzing in, eyes wide open!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Together, Without a Home",
        "Description": "Now that the Tempest is blinded to your whereabouts and actions, the survival of the Soulwardens is starting to become possible. Rejoin them at the temporary refuge scouted out by Grace O'Malley and bring them necessary supplies.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where's everyone else?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "They're west up into the hills, at a fine spot by an overhang. I've just been scouting out the area for Corrupted.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Got some more scouting to do before I head back. I'll see you soon enough.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I didn't expect to see you back among us so soon. Does this mean you found Qi Shen and dispelled the Tempest's spying?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_04a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A New Beginning",
        "Description": "Survival is not enough. The gloom permeating the Soulwarden Refuge is palpable. Find a way with Grace O'Malley to raise morale and remind everyone of the need to keep hope alive.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The loss of Yonas cut him deeply.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I am not unsympathetic. I worry, too. For my friends, and for my Empress. With your return, I feel I should search for her.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will seek out the Empress, wherever she is.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hm. Yash is stepping more lively. The winds are shifting - I have good news - Empress Zhou Taiying has not fallen.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 59,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Empress_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Empress of Ebonscale",
        "Description": "With hope among the Soulwardens rekindled, there remains a need for a powerful ally if they are to overcome the Tempest. Sun Fuchun has won you an audience with the Empress of Ebonscale Reach; meet with her and forge an alliance.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Will she help us?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That is another question. The Empress is a… complex woman with many concerns. I did not see her directly.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Of the tea, I encourage you to gather an appreciable amount. Too little would be insulting; too much would be obsequious.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You are welcome in Ebonscale Reach, Soulwarden. I have heard news of your deeds. Is that a gift you bring for me?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 59,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Empress_01a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Art of War and Friendship",
        "Description": "In order to win the favor of Empress Zhou, it is necessary to perform a ritual on the mountaintop now controlled by the Corrupted. Ascend the peak of Heavenly Rise while lighting incense, and ring the Celestial Bell to reassure the people of Ebonscale Reach that the Empress is still fighting for them.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should be allies.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That would seem to be prudent, yes. But first, I must impose on you for a favor far more precious than any gift.",
        "InProgressResponse": "In times of peace and strife alike, the Celestial Bell is the sound of hope.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "All of Ebonscale now hears the ringing of the Celestial Bell. Surely Aeternum too hears its song. I thank you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 59,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_05a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Lament of the Empress",
        "Description": "Assured of your good intentions and strength, Empress Zhou reveals the tragic story of her family. Work with Sun Fuchun to find a way to heal the pains of the past, and convince the Empress that the Soulwardens are worthy of an alliance with Ebonscale Reach.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should fight it together.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That would be expected, of course. But as is often the case in political matters, there is complexity to contend with.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Poems, as I am sure you are aware, are such heartfelt stories contained in so few words.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "By the light, I have a pit in my stomach. I know that was not easy, but with each moment, the Empress's patience thins.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 59,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Tormented Prince",
        "Description": "With your help, Sun Fuchun has all the ingredients needed to rescue Zhou Liang from his monstrous condition. Meet her at the Wood Shrine and utilize the Soulsever Incense to save him from his prison.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where is the prince?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Prince's location is a secret known only to the Empress, Lingyun, and myself. I now induct you into our confidence.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The trial below must be yours alone. Worry not, from this vantage I can best advise you and stoke the incense further.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You aren't... scared of me. Like everyone else was…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_08a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Return of the Child",
        "Description": "Prince Liang has been saved from his affliction, fulfilling the Soulwarden's commitment to the alliance with Ebonscale Reach. Meet with Empress Zhou atop Serenity Monastery and present her son, healed and finally returned to her.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Would anything help remind you?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Who I was before I… changed… is hazy. I can only remember… images from when I was younger, playing at the broken ships…",
        "InProgressResponse": "There are so many more people in the world… than I remembered.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Glad you're here - I'm in over me head. Managed to sneak up and listen. Seems Isabella went north to gather her forces.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_09",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Fallen Dynasty",
        "Description": "With Empress Zhou fallen to Corruption and determined to sail away from Aeternum, Prince Liang is in danger and so is the rest of the world. On Grace O'Malley's advice, gain access to the Royal Pier and the Empress's ship.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We can't let her set sail.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Then we'll need to move fast. The Empress is already headed for the docks, and that area's locked down tight.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You have the Seals yet? You better hurry! The Empress is about to shove off!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Did you get the Seals? Not a second too soon! They're across the water there - and I spotted the Empress giving that artifact to her captain.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_08",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Mother's Dream",
        "Description": "With access to the Royal Pier attained, Empress Zhou can now be reached and stopped from escaping Aeternum. Confront and defeat her before Ebonscale Reach falls further into Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll deal with the Empress.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A solid plan, but I got an addendum. What say we shut down the Empress's enterprise and then me and you snag that artifact?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Once more unto the beach!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I have only seen and heard a little of what transpired, but I fear to learn this story in full…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99F_Yash_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The New Rising Sun",
        "Description": "Corrupted Empress Zhou is defeated and her tragic ambitions thwarted. In the aftermath of destruction, the Soulwarden have lost a powerful ally. But Prince Liang is safe, and Ebonscale Reach is secure from further Corruption. Debrief with your allies and plan next steps in the fight against the Tempest.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"None of us are immune.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Indeed. Yonas… I now feel Yash's pain, keenly. I owe him an apology, I think.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We will speak in a moment, Warden.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I mourn the loss of Empress Zhou. It seems she was an exemplary leader, but at least there is a path forward.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
